Guide to the Actors' Equity Association Theatrical Programs WAG.257
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series I: New York City, Regional Theatres and Touring Productions/Companies
  - Tap Dance Kid, Undated (Box 48, Folder 5A)
  - Tartuffe, Undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Taste of Honey, Undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Tavern, Undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Tchin-Tchin, Undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Tea and Sympathy, Undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Teahouse of the August Moon, Undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Tecumseh!, Undated (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Teddy & Alice, Undated (Box 48, Folder 12A)
  - Teibele and Her Demon, Undated (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Tempest, Undated (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Ten Little Indians, Undated (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Ten O'Clock Scholar, Undated (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Tenth Man, Undated (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Terra Nova, Undated (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Terry by Terry, Undated (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Texas Trilogy: The Last Meeting of the Knights of the White Magnolia, Lu Ann Hampton Laverty Oberlander, The Oldest Living Graduate, Undated (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - That Championship Season, Undated (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - That's Life, Undated (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - There Shall Be No Night, Undated (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - There's a Girl in My Soup, Undated (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - There's One in Every Marriage, Undated (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - They Knew What They Wanted, Undated (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - They're Playing Our Song, Undated (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Thieve's Carnival, Undated (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - 13 Rue De L'Amour, Undated (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - This is the Army, Undated (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - This Thing Called Love, Undated (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - This Was Burlesque, Undated (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Those the River Keeps, Undated (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Thousand Clowns, Undated (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - Threads, Undated (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - Three Cornered Moon, Undated (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - Three for Tonight, Undated (Box 48, Folder 37)
  - Three Men on a Horse, Undated (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - Three Musketeers, Undated (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - Three on a Runway, Undated (Box 48, Folder 40)
  - Three Penny Opera, Undated (Box 48, Folder 41)
  - Three Sisters, Undated (Box 48, Folder 42)
  - Three Tall Women, Undated (Box 48, Folder 43)
  - Three to Make Ready, Undated (Box 48, Folder 44)
  - Three's a Family, Undated (Box 48, Folder 45)
  - Thurber Carnival, Undated (Box 48, Folder 46)
  - Tiger at the Gates, Undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Till the Day I Die, Undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Timbuktu, Undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Time Limit, Undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Tim of the Cuckoo, Undated (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Time of Your Life, Undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Time Out for Ginger, Undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Time Remembered, Undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Timon of Athens, Undated (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Tin Pan Alley, Undated (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Tintypes, Undated (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Tiny Alice, Undated (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Tip-Toes, Undated (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - 'Tis Pity She's a Whore, Undated (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Titus Andronicus, Undated (Box 49, Folder 14A)
  - To Be Young, Gifted and Black, Undated (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - To Gillian on her 37th Birthday, Undated (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - To Kill a Mockingbird, Undated (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Toad of Toad Hall, Undated (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Tobacco Road, Undated (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Tomfoolery, Undated (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Tommy, Undated (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Tomorrow the World, Undated (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - Tongues, Undated (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - Tonight at 8:30, Undated (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Tons of Money, Undated (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Tony Awards, Undated (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Tony n' Tina's Wedding, Undated (Box 49, Folder 26A)
  - Too Many Girls, Undated (Box 49, Folder 27)
  - Too True to be Good, Undated (Box 49, Folder 28)
  - Tooth of Crime, Undated (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Top Girls, Undated (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - Torch-Bearers, Undated (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Torch Song Trilogy, Undated (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - Total Abandon, Undated (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Touch of the Poet, Undated (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - Tovarich, Undated (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Towards Zero, Undated (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - Toys in the Attic, Undated (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Transcendental Love, Undated (Box 49, Folder 38)
  - Translations, Undated (Box 49, Folder 39)
  - Traveler in the Dark, Undated (Box 49, Folder 40)
  - Travesties, Undated (Box 49, Folder 41)
  - Trelawny of the Wells, Undated (Box 49, Folder 42)
  - Trial, Undated (Box 49, Folder 43)
  - Trial of Mary Dugan, Undated (Box 49, Folder 44)
  - Trial of the Catonsville 9, Undated (Box 49, Folder 45)
  - Tribute, Undated (Box 49, Folder 46)
  - Tricks, Undated (Box 49, Folder 47)
  - Tricks of the Trade, Undated (Box 49, Folder 48)
  - Trip to Bountiful, Undated (Box 49, Folder 49)
  - Triple Play, Undated (Box 49, Folder 50)
  - Trojan Woman, Undated (Box 49, Folder 51)
  - Troilus and Cressida, Undated (Box 49, Folder 52)
  - True West, Undated (Box 49, Folder 53)
  - Twelfth Night, Undated (Box 49, Folder 54)
  - Twelve Dreams, Undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Twentieth Century, Undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Twenty Years: Lucille Lortel's Matinee Series at the Theater de Lys, Dec 1975 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - 29th Street Repertory Theater, Undated (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Twice Around the Park, Undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Two Blind Mice, Undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Two by Five, Undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Two by Two, Undated (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Two for the Seesaw, Undated (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Two Gentlemen of Verona, Undated (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Two Mrs. Carrolls, Undated (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Two Rooms, Undated (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Two Saints, Undated (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Two Small Bodies, Undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Two Trains Running, Undated (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Typists and The Tiger, Undated (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - U, Undated, 1915, 1920s (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - U, 1930s, 1940s (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - U, 1960s (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - U, 1970s (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - U, 1980s (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - U, 1990s, 2000s (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - Ubu/Ubu Rex/Ubu-Roi, Undated (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Ulysses in Nightgown, Undated (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - Uncle Harry, Undated (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Uncle Vanya, Undated (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Uncommon Women and Others, Undated (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Under Milkwood, Undated (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Under Papa's Picture, Undated (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Undiscovered Country, Undated (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Unexpected Guest(s), Undated (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Unknown Soldier and His Wife, Undated (Box 50, Folder 32)
  - Unsinkable Molly Brown, Undated (Box 50, Folder 33)
  - Uptown…it's Hot!, Undated (Box 50, Folder 34)
  - Uproar in the House, Undated (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - U.S.A., Undated (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - Utah Shakespeare Festival, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 37)
  - V, Undated (Box 50, Folder 38)
  - V, 1920s (Box 50, Folder 39)
  - V, 1930s (Box 50, Folder 40)
  - V, 1940s (Box 50, Folder 41)
  - V, 1950s (Box 50, Folder 42)
  - V, 1960s (Box 50, Folder 43)
  - V, 1970s (Box 50, Folder 44)
  - V, 1980s (Box 50, Folder 45)
  - V, 1990s (Box 50, Folder 46)
  - V, 2000s (Box 50, Folder 46A)
  - Vagabond King, Undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Vagabond Stars, Undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Vampire Lesbians of Sodom, Undated (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Vanities, Undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Velvet Glove, Undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Venetian Twins, Undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Veronica's Room, Undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Very Good Eddie, Undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Via Galactica, Undated (Box 51, Folder 8A)
  - Victoria Regina, Undated (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Vienna Lusthaus, Undated (Box 51, Folder 9A)
  - Vieux Carre, Undated (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - View from the Bridge, Undated (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Vikings, Undated (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Vinegar Tree, Undated (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Vintage '60/Vintage'86…the next generation!, Undated (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Virginia, Undated (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Visit, Undated (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Visit to a Small Planet, Undated (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Vivat! Vivat Regina!, Undated (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Voice of the Prairie, Undated (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Voice of the Turtle, Undated (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Voir Dire, Undated (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Volpone, Undated (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Vortex, Undated (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - W, Undated (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - W, 1915 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - W, 1920s (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - W (file 1 of 2), 1930s (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - W (file 2 of 2), 1930s (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - W, 1940s (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - W (file 1 of 2), 1950s (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - W (file 2 of 2), 1950s (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - W (file 1 of 3), 1960s (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - W (file 2 of 3), 1960s (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - W (file 3 of 3), 1960s (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - W (file 1 of 2), 1970s (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - W (file 2 of 2), 1970s (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - W (file 1 of 2), 1980s (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - W (file 2 of 2), 1980s (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - W (file 1 of 2), 1990s (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - W (file 2 of 2), 1990s (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - W, 2000s (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Wait a Minim!, Undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Wait Until Dark, Undated (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Waiting for Godot, Undated (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Waiting for Lefty, Undated (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Waiting Room, Undated (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Wake of Jamey Foster, Undated (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Wake Up, Darling, Undated (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Walk in the Woods, Undated (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Walking Happy, Undated (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Waltz Me Around Again, Undated (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Waltz of the Toreadors, Undated (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Wanted, Undated (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - War and Peace, Undated (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - War Games, Undated (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Watbanaland, Undated (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Watch on the Rhine, Undated (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Water Engine, Undated (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Way of the World, Undated (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - We Bombed in New Haven, Undated (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Wedding Band, Undated (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Wenceslas Square, Undated (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - West Side Story, Undated (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - What Every Woman Knows, Undated (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - What I Did Last Summer, Undated (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - What the Butler Saw, Undated (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - What's a Nice Country Like You Doing in a State Like This?, Undated (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - What's Up, Undated (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - When I was a Girl I Used to Scream and Shout, Undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Where has Tommy Flowers Gone?, Undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Where's Charley?, Undated (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Whispers, Undated (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Whistle in the Dark, Undated (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - White Cargo, Undated (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - White Devil, Undated (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - White Pelicans, Undated (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Who Killed Santa Claus?, Undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Whoopee, Undated (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?, Undated (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Who's Happy Now?, Undated (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Who's Who, Undated (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Whose Life is it Anyway?, Undated (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Why Hanna's Skirt Won't Stay Down, Undated (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Widow Claire, Undated (Box 53, Folder 18A)
  - Wild Duck, Undated (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Wild Oats, Undated (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Will Rogers' Follies, Undated (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Will Success Spoil Rock Hunter, Undated (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Wind in the Willows, Undated (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Winter's Tale, Undated (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Winterset, Undated (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Wish You Were Here, Undated (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Wit, Undated (Box 53, Folder 26A)
  - Within the Gates, Undated (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Witness for the Prosecution, Undated (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Wives, Undated (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Wiz, Undated (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Wizard of Hip, Undated (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Wizard of Oz, Undated (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Woman in Mind, Undated (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Woman of the Year, Undated (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Woman with Red Hair, Undated (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Women, Undated (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Women Beware Women, Undated (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Women's Project, Undated (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - Wonderful Tennessee, Undated (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - Wonderful Town, Undated (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - Wood Demon, Undated (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - Woody Guthrie's American Song, Undated (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - Woolgatherer, Undated (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - Working, Undated (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - World of Sholem Aleichem, Undated (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - World We Make, Undated (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - Would-Be Gentleman, Undated (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - Wuthering Heights, Undated (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - X Has No Value, Undated (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - Y, Undated, 1920s (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - Y, 1930s (Box 53, Folder 51)
  - Y, 1940s (Box 53, Folder 52)
  - Y, 1950s (Box 53, Folder 53)
  - Y, 1960s (Box 53, Folder 54)
  - Y, 1970s (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Y, 1980s (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Y, 1990s (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Y, 2000s (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Yale Repertory Theatre, Undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Yellow Fever, Undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Yentl, Undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Yeoman of the Guard, Undated (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Yerma, Undated (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - You Can't Take It With You, Undated (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - You Know I Can't Hear You When the Water's Running, Undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - You Never Can Tell, Undated (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - You Never Know, Undated (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Young Playwrights Festival, Undated (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Your Arms Too Short to Box with God, Undated (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Your Own Thing, Undated (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Your Room or Mine?, Undated (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - You're a Good Man Charlie Brown, Undated (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Z, Undated (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Ziegfeld American Revue of 1926, Undated (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Ziegfeld Follies(file 1 of 2), 1915, 1920s (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - Ziegfeld Follies(file 2 of 2), 1934-1957 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Ziegfeld Midnight Frolic, Undated (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Ziegfeld "Show Girl", Undated (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Zoo Story, Undated (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Zoot Suit, Undated (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - Zorba, Undated (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - Zulu and the Zayda, Undated (Box 54, Folder 28)
- Series II: Equity Library Theatre, New York City
  - Equity Library Theatre for Children, Undated, 1960s (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Informals, 1960s (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Informals, 1970s (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Informals, 1980s (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Letter to ELT Alumni re: Support, Feb 1975 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Production Lists, Undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Season, 1944-1945 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Season, 1947-1948 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Season, 1948-1949 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Season, 1949-1950 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Season, 1950-1951 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Season, 1951-1952 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Season, 1952-1953 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Season, 1953-1954 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Season, 1954-1955 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Season, 1955-1956 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Season, 1956-1957 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Season, 1957-1958 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Season, 1958-1959 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Season, 1959-1960 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Season, 1960-1961 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Season, 1961-1962 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Season, 1962-1963 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Season, 1963-1964 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Season, 1964-1965 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Season, 1965-1966 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Season, 1966-1967 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Season, 1967-1968 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Season, 1968-1969 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Season, 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Season, 1970-1971 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Season, 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Season, 1972-1973 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Season, 1973-1974 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Season, 1974-1975 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Season, 1975-1976 (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Season, 1976-1977 (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Season, 1977-1978 (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Season, 1978-1979 (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Season, 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - Season, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - Season, 1981-1982 (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - Season, 1982-1983 (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - Season, 1983-1984 (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - Season, 1984-1985 (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - Season, 1985-1986 (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - Season, 1986-1987 (Box 55, Folder 47)
  - Season, 1987-1988 (Box 55, Folder 48)
  - Season, 1988-1989 (Box 55, Folder 49)